So gas, today in this video we will
see about ICICI Lombard Ltd share, the
share price is 1237 and
till now it has given returns of 0.23% in this one day,
whereas if we talk about five days ago, then
five days ago you can see that the shares have
given returns up to zero point 20%
and if we talk about one month, one month the
share has given returns of 8.82%, if we
look at it in six months, then in 6 months the share has
given returns up to 9.82%, whereas if we talk about year to date,
in Airtel date the shares have seen a
decline of 12.6%, if we talk about all time in Max, then
in all time the share has
given returns up to 81.86%, if we
talk about the book value and face value of the share, then
both are very positive, but if we talk about the
yield of this share, then the yield of this share is
not even positive, it is neither negative, neither
less nor more, both are equal, if we
talk about the returns of Airtel, then in 5 years it has given returns of
6  The returns of the share in the month and till one month have been
positive and right now the
returns of this share are moving in six months from one week
but now you can see that they have started
coming positive, so there is
no risk in this share at present,
look at the resistance and support of the stock, its
first support is 1224.63 paise, the second
support
is 121282 paise and the third support is
124.13 paise, the first resistance of this share is
1245.13 paise, the second
resistance is
1253 paise and the third resistance is
1000 to
20065.63 paise. Talking about the share holding of the share, the
promoter has
share holding up to 48.02%, then K has
24.07%, D has 16.03% and the public
has 11.87%, with this share if the share
holding is with the promoter and the
public has the least share holding, the remaining
shares  Holding is with Phir